{
  "questions": [
    {
      "questionText": "In the 'Back To the Future' trilogy, at what speed does the DeLorean need to be going to travel through time?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "100 mph",
        "2": "55 mph",
        "3": "88 mph",
        "4": "1000 mph"
      },
      "correct": "3",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Which is the James Bond film that features the classic line, \"No Mr. Bond, I expect you to die\" ? ",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Goldfinger",
        "2": "From Russia With Love",
        "3": "Live and Let Die",
        "4": "Goldeneye"
      },
      "correct": "1",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "questionText": "What national monument do Cary Grant and Eva Marie Saint find themselves nearly falling off of in 'North by Northwest'?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "The Statue of Liberty",
        "2": "Mount Rushmore",
        "3": "The Washington Monument",
        "4": "The Golden Gate Bridge"
      },
      "correct": "2",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Complete the quote from 'Mean Girls': \"On Wednesdays, ______ \"",
      "answers": {
        "1": "We eat light.",
        "2": "We wear hoop earrings.",
        "3": "We go on dates",
        "4": "We wear pink."
      },
      "correct": "4",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "questionText": "From the movie 'Gremlins' Which is NOT one of the rules for taking care of a Mogwai? ",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Don't feed them after midnight",
        "2": "Don't get them wet",
        "3": "Don't pull on their tail",
        "4": "Don't expose them to bright light."
      },
      "correct": "3",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "questionText": "What is the name of Charles Foster Kane's mansion in 'Citizen Kane'?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Xanadu",
        "2": "Rosebud",
        "3": "Babylon",
        "4": "The Kane Cave"
      },
      "correct": "1",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Which of these Disney Films was nominated for the Academy Award for Best Picture?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
        "2": "Fantasia",
        "3": "The Little Mermaid",
        "4": "Beauty and the Beast"
      },
      "correct": "4",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Which of these Meg Ryan Romantic Comedies does not co-star Tom Hanks? ",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Joe Versus the Volcano",
        "2": "When Harry Met Sally",
        "3": "You've Got Mail",
        "4": "Sleepless in Seattle"
      },
      "correct": "2",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "questionText": " Which rock band provided the soundtrack for the cult classic film, 'Highlander'?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Rush",
        "2": "The Who",
        "3": "Queen",
        "4": "Iron Maiden"
      },
      "correct": "3",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "questionText": "'The Sound of Music' director Robert Wise also directed which '50s Sci-fi classic?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "The Day the Earth Stood Still",
        "2": "Invasion of the Body Snatchers",
        "3": "Forbidden Planet",
        "4": "Plan 9 From Outer Space"
      },
      "correct": "1",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Which NBA Superstar appears as a pilot in the disaster film spoof, 'Airplane!'?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Wilt Chamberlain",
        "2": "Earvin 'Magic' Johnson",
        "3": "Larry Bird",
        "4": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"
      },
      "correct": "4",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Which of these Superheroes is NOT part of the team in the first of the 'Avengers' films?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Iron Man",
        "2": "Spider-man",
        "3": "Thor",
        "4": "Captain America"
      },
      "correct": "2",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "questionText": "The 1995 teen movie 'Clueless' is an updated adaptation of which Jane Austen novel? ",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Emma",
        "2": "Persuasion",
        "3": "Pride and Prejudice",
        "4": "Sense and Sensibility"
      },
      "correct": "1",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Who plays the Monster in 1931's 'Frankenstein'? ",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Bela Lugosi",
        "2": "Lon Chaney",
        "3": "Boris Karloff",
        "4": "Colin Clive"
      },
      "correct": "3",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Al Pacino plays which member of the Corleone family in 'The Godfather' films?",
      "answers": {
        "1": "Vito",
        "2": "Michael",
        "3": "Sonny",
        "4": "Fredo"
      },
      "correct": "2",
      "id": 15
    }
  ],
  "players": [
    {
      "score": 15400,
      "name": "Adam",
      "message": "Movies are fun",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "score": 15100,
      "name": "AMD",
      "message": "Fun game!",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "score": 11700,
      "name": "Marty M.",
      "message": "Heavy Quiz, Doc!",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "score": 16400,
      "name": "Baby",
      "message": "These questions nearly had me in a corner",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "score": 12100,
      "name": "Bruce B.",
      "message": "I smashed it!",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "score": 19600,
      "name": "Andy D.",
      "message": "Get busy quizzing, or get busy trying",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "score": 14300,
      "name": "Eliza D.",
      "message": "I think I got it!",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "score": 11800,
      "name": "Jason V.",
      "message": "...",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "score": 17300,
      "name": "Ron B.",
      "message": "You stay classy, folks!",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "score": 12000,
      "name": "Harry C.",
      "message": "Made my day",
      "id": 10
    }
  ]
}